http://cancerandcareers.org/en/about-us/transparency/privacy-policy

SEARCH
My Favorites (0)
PRIVACY POLICY
At the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers, we respect and protect the privacy of all visitors and users of our web site. The CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers is the sole owner of any information collected on its web site. We do not sell, share or rent this information to others. The CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers collects information from users and visitors to our web site for the sole purpose of analyzing visitor interests, administering the site, tracking movement, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, however, the IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers if you.
The CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers may use the information you provide about yourself to notify you about our programs and services and to respond to your inquiries and requests for information. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to inform you of our programs and services and to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter.
The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities.The CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or in response to a law enforcement agency's request. We may also disclose such information in the event of merger, acquisition, or other business combination. In the event of bankruptcy, the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers will delete such information.
The CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers occasionally has third parties perform services on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, credit card processing, shipping or stocking orders, etc. These third parties have access to your personal information only as needed to perform their services for Cancer and Careers and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the personal information.Although the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers takes appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Statement. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.
For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please send an email, along with your first and last name, to cancerandcareers @ cew.org . You may also opt out of receiving communications from us or request we remove information that you have provided us by sending an email to the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers with your complete name, address and email address.
LINKS
There are hyperlinks throughout the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers site to other related sites which are not under the control of the CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers. These links are provided as a service to our visitors and users and for your reference only. The CEW Foundation / Cancer and Careers is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites hyperlinked or listed as resources on its site. It is your responsibility to review the privacy policy and user conditions of any other web site referred to herein.
COOKIES
To enhance your experience with our site, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to furnish the CEW
Foundation/Cancer and Careers with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. CHILDREN’S PRIVACYWe do not knowingly collect information for anyone under the age of 13. If you know of anyone under the age of 13 whose information is collected or published through our services, or have other concerns about children's privacy, please write to CEW Foundation/Cancer and Careers, 159 West 25th Street, 8th Floor, New York, NY 10001, or email us at cancerandcareers@cew.org.
CHANGES TO POLICYPlease see bottom of page to learn when statement was last updated.
CONTACTIf you have questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy, you can contact the CEW Foundation/Cancer and Careers at:Via regular mail:CEW Foundation/Cancer and Careers159 West 25th Street8th FloorNew York, NY 10001
Via email:cancerandcareers@cew.orgPolicy statement last updated August 3, 2020.
NEWSLETTER SIGN-UP
Sign up to receive the most up-to-date information and resources.
FOLLOW US
Save to Favorites
Your favorites will be saved until you leave the site.
If you would like to store them permanently, please sign in or create an account
Email
Password
Remember Me
Continue as Guest
Help: I forgot my password.
